

C

CONTACT

Phone **021-233-0279**

Email

jeongyunw@gmail.com

Address

Eden Terrace, Auckland

Linkedir

linkedin.com/in/yunwon

Portfolio website **yunwon.github.io**



KEY SKILLS

DESIGN

- UX/UI design
- Graphic design (Print / Digital)

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- HTML5/CSS3 (SCSS)
- Javascript (React JS, Next JS, TypeScript, jQuery)
- Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS
- WordPress(Elementor/Divi)

SOFTWARE

- Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, Indesign, After Effect
- Figma
- Github, VSCode

JEONGYUN WON

GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER / FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Detail-oriented and self-motivated graphic & web designer / front-end web developer with 6 years of experience. With a broad range of skills, I am an expert in designing attractive marketing materials and developing user-friendly/responsive websites using modern technology and tools.



EXPERIENCE

Ingram Micro

May 2021 - present

Graphic designer

- Creating artwork for digital campaigns for various platforms (Social media banner, eDM, print materials), UX design for marketing landing pages
- Building web front-end for eDM, landing page, and microsites using HTML/CSS/Modern CSS frameworks(Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS)

Freelancing

Dec 2019 - present

UX/UI designer and Front-end developer

- Meeting clients to discuss their needs and requirements.
- Planning, wireframing and designing websites across the web and mobile platforms. (Figma)
- Building front-end using React JS / Next JS / TypeScript / HTML5 / CSS3(SCSS) / WordPress.
- Main clients: Bouqo, The History of Egypt Podcast, LotsaGoodies

Toolbox Digital

Aug 2018 - Nov 2019

UI/UX designer and Front-end developer

- Planning, wireframing and designing websites and web apps across the web and mobile platforms. (Adobe XD / UX pin / Figma)
- Building front-end using HTML/CSS/Javascript(mainly React JS)
- Testing, and maintaining functionalities and features across websites and web apps.

Kookmin University Industry-Academic Cooperation Foundation

Mar 2014 - Mar 2016

Graphic designer

• Designing presentation materials, brochures, posters, banners, etc.

Cafe Machebette

Jan 2013 - Jul 2013

Graphic designer

 Designing a wide variety of graphic art and promotional material including packages, posters, catalogs, menus, online banners, interior graphics, etc.



EDUCATION

Feb 2017 - June 2018

Tasman International Academies in New Zealand

Graduate diploma in IT Multimedia

Mar 2008 - Feb 2014

Kookmin University in South Korea

Bachelor's in Visual communication Design